http://www.jigsaw24.com/privacy-notice

You are accessing this website with an out of date browser. Please update to enjoy an optimal experience.
Solutions & Services
Whether you’re looking to deploy Apple in your business, increase digital collaboration in your workplace or
improve your IT infrastructure, our solutions have got you covered. They’re delivered by experts who’ve worked
in your field and are passionate about helping your business meet its objectives with technology.
Read more
The Apple Experience
Why Apple in Business?
Customers
We help businesses, creatives, educational institutions and public sector bodies to
improve their performance through better sustainable technology and expert services,
support and sales. Find out more about the people and organisations we’re proud to work with.
About
We’re one of the UK’s leading B2B technology solutions providers, having delivered amazing levels of
service for nearly 30 years. Find out how we use technology to help our customers solve real-world problems
while delivering projects in a sustainable, responsible way.
Events
Privacy Notice (May 2018)How we use and store your personal dataContactPrivacy Notice (May 2018)How we use and store your personal dataContactWe are Jigsaw24 Limited. We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This notice sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect will be processed by us. Please read this privacy notice carefully to understand our views and practices and your rights regarding your personal data. By visiting https://www.Jigsaw24.com  (our site) your personal information will be processed as described in this notice.For the purpose of data protection legislation, the data controller is Jigsaw24 Limited of The Old Mill, High Church Street, New Basford, Nottingham NG7 7JA.If you have any queries, complaints or requests please contact Neil Box, DevOps, IS&T Director, Jigsaw24 Limited of The Old Mill, High Church Street, New Basford, Nottingham NG7 7JA or DPO@Jigsaw24.com What information do we collect from you?Why do we collect this information?How long do we keep hold of your information?Who might we share your information with?How is your data stored and kept secureWhat are your rights?Changes to this noticeCookiesContact usWhat information do we collect from you?We will collect and process the following data about you:• Information you give us. This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, email, post, fax or otherwise. The information you give us may include your name, job title, address, email address, phone number and financial information.• Information we collect from your use of our site. With regard to each of your visits to our site we will automatically collect the following information:• Technical information, such as the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the Internet, whereabouts you connected to our service, your internet service provider (ISP), aggregated demographic information collected by Google analytics and information about the device you are using to access our service.• Information we collect throughout our relationship. This is information relating to products purchased, repair cases, enquiries, contact details, business sector and marketing preferences.• Information we collect when you visit our offices. This includes CCTV images and video footage of you.• Information we collect when you call us. If you call us we will automatically collect the following information:• The phone number used to call us; and• When we tell you, a recording of inbound and outbound calls.• Information we receive from other sources. We are working closely with other organisations, including:• Credit check providers;• Publicly available resources including online sources;• Marketing list providers for email, print or telephone campaign;• From our suppliers in order to support the products/services we sell you; and• Data matching as required to maintain the accuracy of personal information provided.• Providing us with your details online. This is information you may choose to provide us when using our site. It includes your name, job title, address, telephone number, email address and preferences for receiving marketing emails, telephone calls and mail from us. Please let us know if any of this information changes so we can keep our records up to date.Why do we collect this information?We process your personal information for the following reasons:• Pursuant to a contract in order to:• Process information at your request to take steps to enter into a contract;• Provide you with our products and services;• Provide you with a quote for our products and services;• Process payments;• Make deliveries;• Maintain business and service continuity;• Send service communications so that you receive a full and functional service and so we can perform our obligations to you. These may be sent by email or post or, if the circumstances require it, we may contact you by phone or fax. These will include notifications about changes to our service;• Assist with technical repairs; and• Record information to facilitate your rights under warranty services.• On the basis of your consent:• Where we rely on your consent for processing this will be brought to your attention when the information is collected from you;• Where you are a prospect or a new consumer we will only contact you with direct marketing communications if you consent to us doing so and you have the right to withdraw consent at any time. See the What are your rights? section below for more information.• In our legitimate interests of providing the best service and improving and growing our business we will process information in order to:• In order to carry out marketing activities where you are a new or existing customer;• Provide you with a personalised service;• Improve our products and services;• Keep our site and systems safe and secure;• Understand our customer base and purchasing trends;• Defend against or exercise legal claims and investigate complaints; and• Understand the effectiveness of our marketing.We will carry out analytics to improve our products and services as set out above.You have the right to object to processing carried out for our legitimate interests. See the What are your rights? section below for more information.• To comply with legal requirements relating to:• The provision of products and services;• Data protection;• Health and safety;• Anti-money laundering;• Fraud investigations;• Assisting law enforcement; and• Any other legal obligations placed on us from time to time.How long do we keep hold of your information?• We will keep personal information about you for a maximum of 7 years after the end of our relationship with you unless obligations to our regulators require otherwise or we are required to remove such data from our records. After this time, we will pseudonymise your personal information.• We will remove your personal information, if you or your organisation have never purchased from Jigsaw24, and are no longer subscribed or engaged with our marketing, after 1 year.• We will remove your data, on request, as aligned to your rights as a Data Subject, unless obligations to our regulators require otherwise.• We retain contact details to enable us to send you marketing information for as long as we have your consent or (if relying on legitimate interests) for as long as our legitimate interests allow.• Telephone records. We will keep these up to 6 months from the time the recording was made.Who might we share your information with?For the purposes set out in the ‘Why do we collect this information?’ section above, we will share your personal information with:• The following categories of third parties, some of whom we appoint to provide services, including:• Business partners, subsidiaries, suppliers, IT suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with you;• Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site;• Courier service providers to ensure the delivery of your products;• Customer survey providers in order to receive feedback and improve our services;• Credit check providers; and• Any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries.• Additionally, we will disclose your personal information to the relevant third party:• In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.• If we are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.• If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers, our regulator, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection, prevention of money laundering and credit risk reduction.How is your data stored and kept secure?At Jigsaw24 Limited, we take your safety and security very seriously and we are committed to protecting your personal and financial information. All information kept by us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain parts of our service, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.We may transfer your data outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). We will only do so if adequate protection measures are in place in compliance with data protection legislation. We use the following protection measures:• Transferring to Commission approved countries;• Using Commission approved model contractual clauses;• Requiring companies we transfer data to in the USA to be signed up to certification e.g. Privacy Shield for US.Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.What are your rights and how can you access the information we hold about you?Where processing of your personal data is based on consent, you can withdraw that consent at any time.You have the following rights. You can exercise these rights at any time by contacting us at FAO Data Protection Officer, Jigsaw24 Limited, 40 High Church Street, New Basford, Nottingham NG7 7JA; DPO@Jigsaw24.com .  You have the right:• To ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes;• To ask us not to process your personal data where it is processed on the basis of legitimate interests provided that there are no compelling reasons for that processing;• To ask us not to process your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes, where relevant, unless the processing is necessary in the public interest.• To request from us access to personal information held about you;• To ask for the information we hold about you to be rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete;• To ask for data to be erased provided that the personal data is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, you withdraw consent (if the legal basis for processing is consent), you exercise your right to object, set out below, and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for processing, the data is unlawfully processed, the data needs to be erased to comply with a legal obligation or the data is children’s data and was collected in relation to an offer of information society services;• To ask for the processing of that information to be restricted if the accuracy of that data is contested, the processing is unlawful, the personal data is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or you exercise your right to object (pending verification of whether there are legitimate grounds for processing);• To ask for data portability if the processing is carried out by automated means and the legal basis for processing is consent or contract.Should you have any issues, concerns or problems in relation to your data, or wish to notify us of data which is inaccurate, please let us know by contacting us using the contact details above. In the event that you are not satisfied with our processing of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority, which is the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) in the UK, at any time.  The ICO’s contact details are available here: https://ico.org.uk/concerns/.Changes to our privacy noticeThis notice may be updated from time to time. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy notice.CookiesFurther Questions If you have any further questions regarding this Privacy Notice, please contact us by email on DPO@Jigsaw24.com
